ILR School Conference Center Group Photographs from Conferences /4275 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Conference Center Group Photographs from Conferences
1990- 2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR). Conference Center
/4275 P
0.33 cubic feet
0.3 linear ft.
Photographs.
Photos from IBEW, CWA, NYSUT and Old International Teams.
7935441
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 02, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of photos from IBEW, CWA, NYSUT and Old International Teams. Also included are staff members from the ILR Extension Staff and Faculty, Off Campus College, Labor Summer Schools, and many photos that have no labelling.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Communications Workers of America -- Photographs; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers -- Photographs; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations -- Photographs; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Conference Center -- Photographs; New York State United Teachers -- Photographs
7935441
- BMC -- 9-80-94 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1 photograph
- BMC -- 10-6-93 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sept. 22-27, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous - unlabeled (Box 1, Folder 4)
  8 photographs
- Contact sheets for ff4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- List of names and locations for a photograph 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ILR Extension Staff and Faculty (Box 1, Folder 7)
  6 photographs
- ILR Off Campus College (Box 1, Folder 8)
  7 photographs
- ILR Labor Summer School (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ILR Summer Schools (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous - Unlabeled photographs (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous - Unlabeled photographs (Box 1, Folder 12)
  4 photographs
- Miscellaneous - Unlabeled photographs (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous - unlabeled photographs (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Nov. 4-8, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Oct. 5-9, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- NYSUT/Cornell Leadership Institute 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- NYSUT Pictures -- July 9-14, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- CWA/Clara L. Allen Leadership Training -- Sept. 27-Oct. 1, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- NYSUT/Cornell Leadership Institute 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- NYSUT/Cornell Leadership Institute 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- CWA pictures (Box 1, Folder 22)
  5 photographs
- IBEW Oct.31-Nov. 2, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)